Listen, we are going to see how to configure our ATC to work with the DNA.
So I've created a new project, Enough Cloud Helping Out.
Let's get started.
So we are going to use our P, uh, our ATC Channel Zero, which is P0 of our esteemed 32 F board.
So select P is you hear us input Channel zero.
It is one input, zero configuration.
What I'm gonna do is, um, I'm going to set a clock so that you works for F zero four zero one as well
as F one one.
If I leave it like this it would work for everyone.
But because I don't want us to have all foreseen issues when some other person is using F zero one F
for actually it at four zero one, then I'm just gonna set it to the default of Air Force One.
So come here it I and then this goes to sixteen and um I'm just gonna sit here two sixteen as well.
I selected as I here and then I'm just changing this peripheral clock to sixteen.
Right.
And it's going to go through that.
And once that's done we can come back to pin and configuration and then deal with the ATC configuration,
click ATC over here and then I'll open it from here.
See?
Click here to open, so.
Yeah.
Channel zero.
How can I go by your parameter settings?
So to continuously convert values from the ADC channel using the DME.
First we have to set a continuous mode because we want it to be continuous.
Let's see continuous mode over here enabled and then a continuous request.
The reason why this is like this is because we've got a going at our DNA first.
So come to image settings and then I'm going to add select ABC one.
OK.
So then I go back to parameter settings and then give me continuous requests.
Now the dropdown allows me to see a neighborhood.
And one last would within D.M. Hour channel.
We have to know so we can increase the number of Cycos a bit.
Also like this one.
Eighty four cycles.
Right.
So we can go back to our DMV settings and complete it.
OK.
Everything here makes sense.
We know we are taken from the peripheral and storing it in memory, meaning we are reading from the,
um, the ATC, which is a peripheral storing.
They read Vudu into memory.
We read a value to store it in the memory so that direction is peripheral to memory.
Aubagio, we want to make it a secular buffer so that it continues all the time.
It doesn't just end when it reaches the end.
It's secular.
Right.
And the data with Yeah.
Is a sixteen bit half word data size, which is fine because we've selected our, uh, ADC because our
aid is just running on top of it.
So yeah, it's within the largest of bits.
Number is four thousand and ninety six.
So yeah, this falls within the range of the half word that we have selected over here.
We need not change it.
Right.
So now we can go ahead and generally talk with a click with a huge rate and then I'll give this a name.
ATC on that score at the end like this, also added to change is the SDM 32 Kubota E..
Click here to generate.
So this is a project of clean up a bit.
Yeah.
Clean up a bit of the comment.
And as you can see, we have our eight is one in eight.
And the DMA in it.
Right.
So over here, we simply need to use the whole ADC starts DME API to start our ADC with Yemi.
And we've got to create a buffer to start it.
Um, the conversion.
So I'm going to come over here and see you end 16 on squatty and then I call this sense of volume.
It's a single value.
And it's a size of one.
Cos we've got this one ADC channel we are working with.
So I'll come down here then and then I'll call our function.
That is all on this call.
ADC on this call.
Start on the score, DME, and then the first argument is the handle is the, um, under 40 ADC, which
is each ADC one.
And then the second argument is the, um, the buffer to store the, um, the ADC value.
The name of the buffer is sense of value.
And, you know, the size is one.
But we've got to typecast this to you in 32.
The function expects a you in thirty two point.
So you enter thirty two on this call to start over here and put some code on here.
So when we run this, we should see our ADC value whenever the sample, the sampling is complete from
our peers.
You when we connect our sense what to P is your what.
It s a temperature sensor or hot reaction.
So pressure sensor, et cetera.
Whenever you notice a new something complete, we should see it stored in this array here.
If we want to be notified when the sampling is complete so that we take a particular action, such as
run a particular algorithm, let's say we want to be notified that sampling is complete.
Today, the sample, we can use a callback function for something like that without a callback.
We will still get our ADC value if we want to get a notification when the sampling is complete.
Then we can implement a callback function and put a block of wood.
We want to execute when when the sampling is complete.
OK.
Right.
So let's go and get a callback.
We know how to get a callback.
We just go to the module we're dealing with is the drivers and then the source we're dealing with PTC.
So we select PD.
You don't see far out of here.
And then, uh, what we going to do?
A search a week to work on a school, on the school week, and then we go through them one by one.
And then there is this Kobuk version, complete Kobuk.
This is the notification for complete.
The conversion is complete.
If even if it's half complete, we can still be notified.
So we execute a block of code.
Well, we can just use the complete.
You can experiment.
We have complete on your own.
So copy this.
Come over here.
And then, um, I just paste this.
Yeah.
But we don't have to do anything here.
If you have an entity to blink or something to a puzzle to sound, you can do it.
I'll just tell you to do something here.
Just do something, you know, like this.
OK.
So we can grow in, um, Londis and then check the check the expressions view whether indeed we can
see our ADC value when um when we connect connected senso.
So click here to build our project.
It's built successfully.
Click here to go to the debark.
It's open in.
This is a project we can learn everything from the live expression.
This is from a previous project.
I'm going to add our sense of value here to live expression.
Like this.
And for those of you using the nuclear board, this is the location of P es u p es you.
Is this paying off?
Yeah, this one here is P is euro, so you can connect your sense.
Oh, here I can just connect a potential meter.
And then just turn it so to the.
So I'm going to put a break point in here.
My wife, I want to loop.
There's the break point and we have this.
Yeah, I've connected.
I've connected a potential meetup to my peers.
You click here to run.
And then I'll click again.
And I'm going to expand this.
And this is our sense of value.
So there's so to quote, forgot the ADC for DME transfer.
Do you have any questions?
Live in the community and I'll see you later.
Have a nice day.